<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Goblin\'s Head Tavern</string>
    <string name="general_text">
        <![CDATA[

                <h1>Welcome to The Goblin\'s Head </h1>
                <h4><font color="#ffffff">Reserve your table today!</font></h4>

                </br>
                <p>The Goblin\'s Head is the pub in the otherwise un-named village where Sam
                Vimes gets used to being Lord of the Manor and a real Squire because he owns the
                place. Mine host is the suspiciously eager-to-please Jiminy, and Sam notes an
                adornment of the wall, among all the legitimate hunting trophies, is a real goblin\'s head. </P>

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_text">
        <![CDATA[

                <h1>Our Menu</h1>
                <h4><font color="#ffffff">The freshest products Ankh-Morpork can provide</font></h4>
                </br>
                <p>Discworld haute cuisine, in all it\'s glory. A simple rule for dining
                on Discworld: if it\'s sold by anyone whose last name sounds a bit like "Dibbler", don\'t go near it. </P>
                <p><i>We offer: <br>
                    - Captain Eightpanther\'s Travellers\' Digestives <font color="#ffffff">$13.50</font><br>
                    - Sausage-in-a-bun <font color="#ffffff">$5.99</font><br>
                    - Milknut-meal <font color="#ffffff">$3.99</font><br>
                    - Banged Grains <font color="#ffffff">$1.50</font><br>
                    - Meatpie Floater <font color="#ffffff">$8.99</font><br>
                    - Brownish Ale <font color="#ffffff">$1</font><br>
                    - Root Beer <font color="#ffffff">$0.89</font><br></i>
                </p>


        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="contact_text">
        <![CDATA[

                <big>How To Find Us</big>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="host_text">
        <![CDATA[
                <h2>Your Host</h2>
                <p><b><font color="#ffffff">Samuel "Sam" Vimes</font></b> is a fictional policeman from Terry Pratchetts <i>Discworld</i> series.
                Vimes is depicted in the novels as somewhere between an Inspector-Morse-type old-school British policeman,
                and a film-noir-esque grizzled, jaded detective. <p>His appearances throughout the Discworld sequence
                show him slowly and grudgingly rising through the ranks of both police force and society.</p>
                <p>As of his latest promotion, his full name and title is: "<i>His Grace, His Excellency, The Duke of Ankh;
                Commander Sir Samuel Vimes</i>"</p>
                <p>When serving as Ambassador for Ankh-Morpork, he is also referred to simply as "<i>His Excellency</i>",
                and is also nicknamed
                "<i>Blackboard Monitor Vimes</i>", "Vimes the Butcher/Butcher Vimes" and "<i>Vetinari\'s Terrier</i>"
                (or his <i>hammer</i>, depending upon the occasion): According to his wife, Sybil, Vimes
                is recognised by many as Lord Vetinari\'s right-hand man.</p>



        ]]>
    </string>

</resources>
